Liao of the Six Great Generals... was a woman.
And...
she was going to be Wang Qi's wife.
The setting is before the common era, in the Spring and Autumn Warring States Period.
Xin, the boy that came from obscurity to become the general of a Hundred-Man Unit
is now at the center of a historic battle.
A one-on-one battle between the State of Qin Supreme Commander, Wang Qi,
and the State of Zhao Supreme Commander, Pang Nuan.
Gripped in that deeply personal battle
rests the fate of a kingdom.
Presented by Anime-Destiny
（昌文君(しょうぶんくん)）六将 摎(きょう)は女でした
itsumo yori hayaku kietetta hoshi zora ni
いつもより早く消えてった星空に
In a starry sky that disappeared faster than it ever has
Translation
kewl0210
（昌文君）そして…
kusanariatta deai wa
重なり合った出会いは
the many piled up meetings we've had
Editing
jagman1x3
王騎(おうき)の
妻になるはずの女だったのです
ore wo nomikonde iku
俺を呑み込んでいく
swallow me.
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）時は紀元前 春秋戦国時代
kono yume wa kudakenai
この夢は砕けない
This dream cannot be broken.
Timing
rtrs
名もなき存在から
百人隊の将にまでなった少年 信(しん)は
sabitsukaseta kyoufushin
錆びつかせた恐怖心
Among this rusted fear in my heart
yuragu fuan no naka de
揺らぐ不安の中で
and the anxiety that makes me waver
Typesetting
kewl0210
今 歴史的な戦いの中心にいた
ame wo saegiru shinjitsu
雨を遮る信実
is a truth that interrupts the rain.
秦国(しんこく)総大将 王騎と
趙国(ちょうこく)総大将 龐煖(ほうけん)の一騎打ち
dare ni mo ubaeyashinai
誰にも奪えやしない
No one can take it away,
Karaoke
kewl0210
FZeroWing
onaji keshiki ni hisonda puraido
同じ景色にひそんだプライド
our pride that lurks in the same landscape.
因縁深き その戦いに
国家の命運が握られていた
Encode
max80
itsuka kitto kanau ima mo mieru kibou fortitude
いつかきっと叶う 今も見える希望 fortitude
The fortuitous desire I have will definitely come true one day.
yowasa wo sute wa shinai
弱さを捨てはしない
We won't throw away our weaknesses,
oretachi no kienai shiin
俺達の消えないシーン
those are scenes that won't disappear.
furenzokusen no youni hashiru kibou unbreakable heart
不連続線の様に走る希望 unbreakable heart
My desire in my unbreakable heart runs like a discontinuous line.
I knew at the start that there's no end.
QC
Mistral[sA]
I've made up my mind, right now it's the time to take the first step.
Distro
kokus
Kittie
prefix-
Now's the only time.
～♪
Wang Qi and Liao
（政(せい)）
摎が王騎の妻になるはずだった女？
Liao was a woman and was going to be Wang Qi's wife...?
（政）いや 六大将軍のひとりが
女だったというのか？
No... You're saying that one of the Six Great Generals was a woman?!
Yes, now I'll tell you everything.
はい
今こそ全てをお話ししましょう
私が摎と出会ったのは
随分と前のことになります
I met Liao a long, long time ago.
At the time, the State of Qin and the State of Zhao were in fierce contention with each other.
当時も秦国は
趙国と激しく敵対していました
The long war ended in the State of Qin's victory,
長平(ちょうへい)の戦いこそ
秦国の勝利で終わったものの―
まだ各地に戦いの火種が
いくらでも くすぶっていました
but there were many places where the embers of war still smoldered.
そんな時代でした
That was the kind of age it was.
（兵士Ａ）若殿！ 昌文君さま！
（昌文君）うん？
Young Lord!
Lord Changwenjun!
General Wang Qi's army has arrived!
（兵士Ａ）
王騎将軍の軍が到着しました！
（兵士Ｂ）な… 何ですか？
あの異様な風体の軍は…
Wh-Who are they?!
That... odd-looking army...
フン…
ただの目立ちたがりのアホどもだ
They're just a bunch of fools that want to show off.
女？
A woman?!
（昌文君）その娘こそ 女兵士 摎
That young woman was the female soldier Liao.
Her looks belied the fact that she was professed to be a warrior that put men to shame.
美しい顔だちに見合わぬ―
男顔負けの
武人という触れ込みでした
聞けば そもそも
王騎の屋敷の召し使いの子であると
When I inquired, I learned that she had originally been a servant girl at Wang Qi's residence.
（政）召し使いの子？
（昌文君）はい
Servant girl?
Yes, I also heard that she had been near Wang Qi since her childhood and polished her martial arts skills on her own...
幼少のころより王騎の近くで育ち
自ら武術の腕前を磨いたとか
無論
私も信用しておりませなんだが
Of course, I did not believe those things, however.
What is all the commotion?
何を騒いでおる？
（兵士Ａ）あっ… それが…
Ah, well...
（昌文君）
えっ？ 趙雷(ちょうらい)と国要(こくよう)を討っただと？
She killed Zhao Lei and Hei Yao?!
（兵士Ｂ）
て… 敵の大将と副将じゃないか！
Th-Those are the enemy's Great General and Vice General, aren't they?
Since then, I went to the battlefield with her countless times
（昌文君）それから何度となく
戦場を共にするようになりました
そして その度に―
and when I did, I learned the strength of the girl called Liao.
摎という娘の強さを
思い知ることとなったのです
（摎）じい！ じいは左をつぶせ！
Old man!
Old man, take the left!
わ… 若殿…
（昌文君）誰が じいか！
Y-Young Lord!
Who's an old man?!
Let's go! To the left!
いくぞ！ 左だ！
（兵士Ａ）は… はっ！
Ah, yes, sir!
In both military force and in strategy
（昌文君）
武を取っても策を取っても―
摎は正に戦の天才だったのです
Liao was truly a war prodigy.
And...
そして…
Our king, feared throughout the states as God of War,
（王騎）列国に
“戦神(いくさがみ)”と恐れられる我が王は―
前線を度々訪れるほどの戦好き
loves war so much he sometimes visits the front lines...
He's been leaving the royal palace to go to campaigns quite often.
王宮を離れ
遠征に出るのは昔からです
That is quite reassuring.
（昌文君）頼もしいことだ
（王騎）ええ
Yes.
しかし
男たちが外で戦っている裏でも―
But while men are fighting on the outside, there are conflicts going on behind the scenes as well...
争いは起こっています
（王騎）場所は後宮
In the inner palace.
（昌文君）王騎が言うように―
As Wang Qi said, at that time, the inner palace was particularly turbulent.
そのころの後宮は
特に荒れておりました
世継ぎの問題を巡り―
Bloody conflict over the heir to the throne was unending.
血なまぐさい争いが
絶えなかったのです
昭王(しょうおう)が王宮を離れがちなことが
それに拍車をかけていました
King Zhao's tendency to leave the palace only spurred that on.
And remarkably, among such circumstances, a beautiful palace girl that the king had taken favor to
（昌文君）そんな中で ひときわ
王の寵愛(ちょうあい)を受けていた美しい宮女が
was carrying a child.
子を宿しました
しかし その女は
下級の武家の出だったのです
But that woman was from a low-class warrior family.
（昌文君）後宮において
後ろ盾になってくれる者も見込めず
In the inner palace, she could not expect anyone to support her
and she was wholly unable to protect her child.
とても赤子を守ることなど
できはしませんでした
そこで 彼女は…
So, she...
I'm sorry... I'm so sorry...
（宮女）ごめん… ごめんね…
こうするしか… ないの…
This is my only... choice...
ごめんね…
I'm sorry...
Please... Grow up in good health...
どうか健やかに…
摎…
Liao...
（昌文君）摎の母は信頼できる所へ
我が子を託したのです
Liao's mother entrusted her child to a place where it would be safe.
王宮から離れた地 なおかつ
事情を理解できる地位の人間
A place far away from the royal palace
and with people who would understand the circumstances she was in...
（昌文君）つまり 王騎の屋敷です
In other words, she was brought to Wang Qi's residence.
Liao's mother the daughter of one of Wang Qi's father's comrade in arms.
摎の母は
王騎の父の戦友の娘でした
Though because adopting a daughter so suddenly would draw attention, she was taken in as a servant.
…とはいえ
突然 養女にするのは目立つため
召し使いの子として
（政）
まさか 六将 摎が昭王の娘とは…
I can't believe that Six General Liao was King Zhao's daughter...
その事実 昭王や摎は？
Did King Zhao and Liao know that fact?
（昌文君）
もちろん知りませんでした
Of course, they did not know...
However...
ところが…
（兵士）
大王さまがいらっしゃった！
The king is coming!
Hurry, get in line!
急げ！ 列を整えろ！
ボケッとするな！
Don't just stand there!
One day, King Zhao showed himself at the battlefield.
（昌文君）ある日のこと
戦場に昭王が姿を見せられたのです
南安(なんあん)での戦いを勝利に
導いた王騎軍をねぎらうために
It was to thank the Wang Qi Army for leading them to victory in the battle at Nanan.
（昭王）
さすがは王騎！ 我が宝刀よ
Just what I've come to expect from you, Wang Qi, my treasured sword!
（昭王）この南安は―
This land of Nanan was an unassailable land that we could not obtain for many long years.
長年 手に入れることがかなわぬ
不落の地であった
誠に よくやったぞ！
You have truly outdone yourself!
I humbly thank you for the kind words.
身に余るお言葉
ありがたくいただきます
うん？ どうした？ 摎
What's wrong, Liao?
う… うん 何でもない
Ah, nothing.
（昭王）
ところで王騎 あの者は どこじゃ？
Speaking of which, Wang Qi, where is that person?
今回も活躍したそうではないか
They were quite active in this campaign as well, weren't they?
お前の側近の女兵士 摎
Your close aide, the woman soldier, Liao.
最近 よくその名を耳にするぞ
I've been hearing that name quite a bit lately.
どこにおるのじゃ？
Where might she be?
摎 前へ
Liao, come forward.
は… はい！
Y-Yes, sir!
（兵士たちの ざわめき）
Liao... How old are you?
（昭王）摎… 年はいくつだ？
じゅ… 16です
S-Sixteen, sir.
そうか…
I see... I see...
そうか
よく頑張ったな
You've fought hard.
摎 王騎同様―
Liao... Just like Wang Qi...
you are my treasure.
お前も私の宝だ
もちろん うぬら全員もだ！
As, of course, are all of you!
帰ったら 必ず褒美を取らせるぞ
（兵士たちの歓声）
When you return, you will have a great reward waiting!
（昭王）王騎
（王騎）はい
Wang Qi.
Yes, sir?
（昭王）あとで話がある
（王騎）はっ！
I have something to talk to you about later.
Yes, sir.
And after that, Liao started wearing a mask on the battlefield.
（昌文君）そして それから―
摎は戦場で
仮面を着けるようになりました
表向きの理由は―
The reason for the change in appearance
was that she wanted to hide the fact that she was a woman before her name was known throughout the states.
列国に名の通る前に
女であることを隠すためでしたが
摎について その素性を語ることも
禁じられたのです
But for Liao, telling her lineage was something she could not do.
（昌文君）
そして それからまもなく―
And not long before that, Liao was formally made a general.
摎は正式に将に列せられました
Liao, do you have a moment?
（昌文君）摎 少しいいか？
（摎）じいか？ どうぞ
Is that you, old man? Come in.
誰が じいか
Who's an old man?
平気なのか？
Are you doing all right?
（摎）やっとね
気持ちの整理がついてきた
Yes, finally. I've gotten my emotions in order.
怒りも悲しみもないよ
I'm not angry nor sad.
だって 本当は
すぐに殺されてた命だもんね
I mean, I may be killed at any time, after all.
こうして生きてるだけで感謝だよ
I'm grateful I'm just able to live this way.
Yeah, that's a lie.
うん ウソ　本当は すごく悲しい…
To be honest, I'm incredibly sad.
じいは王騎さまから話を？
（昌文君）ああ…
Did you hear everything from Wang Qi, old man?
Yes.
（摎）そっか
I see!
貧乏クジだね
どうりで出世できないわけだ
You really got the short end of the stick.
No wonder you can't get any success in life.
（昌文君）やかましい
（摎）フフッ…
Cut it out!
You're a woman.
お前は女だ
軍としては大損失だが―
It would be a big loss for the army,
ここで剣を置くのも
ひとつの道だろう
but you also have the choice putting down your sword here.
それは本末転倒だよ
私が剣を置いて何が残るの？
That would be getting the cart before the horse.
If I put down my sword, what would I have left?
公女になれるわけでもない
ただの召し使いの娘
It's not like I could become a princess.
I'm just the daughter of a servant.
剣は置かない
I can't put down my sword.
だが 戦い続けて どうするのだ？
But what do you plan to do by continuing to fight?
天下の大将軍になる！
Become the greatest general under the heavens!
な… なんだと？
What?!
私の戦う理由はね
It's my reason for fighting.
本当に たわいもない
子供のころの約束なんだ
It's a really silly promise I made when I was a child.
（摎）王騎さま！
Lord Wang Qi!
When you become the greatest general under the heavens, will you capture lots of castles?
王騎さまは天下の大将軍になって
お城をたくさん取るんですか？
（王騎）ンフフフッ… そうですよ
Yes, I suppose.
Then I'm going to become a Great General, too!
（摎）
それでは 摎も大将軍になります！
そして お城を100コ取ったら
摎を王騎さまの妻にしてください！
And when I've captured 100 castles, please let me be your wife, Lord Wang Qi!
（王騎）ンフフフッ… いいですよ
（摎）わあ！
All right.
エヘッ…
（摎）
“ああ くだらん”とか言わないの
He didn't say anything like "That's ridiculous!"
子供のころの私は
大真面目だったんだから
because when I was a child I was really serious.
そして 今も大真面目
And I still am now.
My place is here, the battlefield, old man.
私の居場所は ここだよ じい
I have lots of comrades here as well.
仲間もいっぱいいる
それに
これからは父も見ていてくれる
And now, my father will be watching me as well.
私は やるぞ
I'm going to do it!
Flag : Liao
（昌文君）ひと度 火蓋を切ると
With her severe fighting style of never relenting in her attack until the enemy was destroyed,
敵を滅するまで攻撃をやめない
苛烈な戦いぶりで―
摎は勝ち続けました
Liao continues to gain victories.
（昌文君）将軍となって すぐ―
Soon after she became a general, her strength was said to rival that of the Five Great Generals.
その力は秦の五大将軍に匹敵すると
言われるまでになっておりました
And finally, Liao was named as the sixth Great General.
（昌文君）そして 摎は ついに
６人目の大将軍となったのです
摎が大将軍となって
しばらくしたころ…
Then, not long after Liao became a Great General...
（兵士Ｃ）お… 王騎さまだ！
（兵士Ｄ）王騎将軍！
It-It's Lord Wang Qi!
General Wang Qi!
（兵士Ｅ）
昌文君どのもいらっしゃるぞ！
Lord Changwenjun is coming as well!
（王騎）入りますよ
We're coming in.
久しぶりだな 摎…
It's been quite a while.
Liao-
（王騎）ンフッ…
お… 王騎さま！
L-Lord Wang Qi!
あ… あの…
U-Um...
I'll do that myself...
（摎）
そんなことは自分でやりますから…
Didn't I always use to treat your wounds like this?
昔はよく
こうして手当てしてあげたものです
When are you talking about?!
（摎）いつの話ですか
I'm not a child anymore!
摎は もう子供じゃありませんよ
本当に久しぶりですね 摎
It really has been quite a while, hasn't it, Liao...?
誰かと違って 大きく出世すると
なかなか自由がありませんからね
Unlike someone I could mention, you've gained great success, and with that, you do not have much freedom.
はい…
Yes.
（王騎）はい
There.
U-Um, Lord Wang Qi...
あ… あの… 王騎さま
あっ いえ… 何でも…
No, never mind...
ところで 何用で ここに？
By the way, why did you come to see me?
（王騎）久々に あなたに
会いたくなって 遠路はるばる…
I just came all this way because I wanted to see you again after so long.
…というのは冗談で
次の戦のためです
No, just kidding. It's about the next war.
The next war?
次の戦？
（王騎）次の戦 馬陽(ばよう)攻略戦は―
For the next war, the siege of Mayang,
it's been decided that my forces and yours would form a coalition.
あなたと私の連合軍で
戦うことになりました
王騎さまと私で？
You and I, Lord Wang Qi?!
（昌文君）
一応 わしの軍も参加するがな
For now, my army will be participating as well, though.
I will be the vice general and you will be the Great General, Liao.
（王騎）
私は副将 大将はあなたです
摎…
いよいよ最後の１つですね
We're finally at the last one, aren't we?
“最後の１つ”？ うん？ 何だ？
Last one?
What?
What's wrong, Liao?
どうした？ 摎
覚えていてくださったんだ…
しかも 数まで…
He remembered.
And even after how many...
えっ？ まさか…
You don't mean...
（摎）そして お城を100コ取ったら
摎を王騎さまの妻にしてください！
And when I've captured 100 castles, please let me be your wife, Lord Wang Qi!
（王騎）ンフフフッ… いいですよ
All right.
うん そうなの… 次の馬陽の城で…
That's right...
This next castle at Mayang will be the 100th.
100コ目なんだ
（昌文君）しかし 馬陽攻略の前夜
あの男が現れたのです
But on the night before the siege of Mayang, that man appeared.
That man that is like a disaster in the form of a human...
まるで人の形をした災厄のような
あの男が…
（信）どうしたんだ？
王騎将軍が動かねえ
What's going on? General Wang Qi... isn't moving...
（信）ウワッ！
（渕(えん)）こ… これは！
Wh-What is this?!
This is it!
（龐煖）これだ
これと戦うために俺は来た！
This is what I came here to fight.
９年前に敗れた これと…
This which I lost to 9 years ago...
Pang Nuan. Even I do not know what it is that man wished to do.
（昌文君）龐煖…
あの男が何をしたかったのか―
私には分かりません
野営地の兵士たちを斬り倒し
摎に襲いかかった
He cut through soldiers at their campsite and attacked Liao.
ただ強きを求めるように…
Like he was merely seeking strength...
Lord Liao!
（摎軍兵たち）摎さま！ 摎将軍！
General Liao!
Lord Liao!
（摎）ハアッ！
（摎軍兵たち）摎さま！ 摎さま！
Lord Liao!
General Liao!
There can be only one on earth that the heavens fear.
（龐煖）天の恐るる者は
地上に ただひとり　我だけだ
Me and me alone.
（兵士）王騎将軍！
General Wang Qi!
（龐煖）もう１人おったか！
There was another?!
（兵士たち）ウワッ！
（龐煖）なんだ この男の力は…
What is this man's strength?!
ハアーッ！
（王騎軍兵）射(う)て！
（刺さる音）
Fire!
（龐煖）グワッ！
なぜだ… なぜ敗れた？
Why...
Why did I lose...?
あの女に受けた傷のせいか？
Is it because of the wounds I suffered from that woman?
No... The wounds were of no relevance.
違う… 傷など関係ない
That man was stronger...
あの男のほうが上だったのだ
My might could not reach him!
我が武が及ばなかったのだ
我が武が！
My fighting strength!
来い 王騎！
今の貴様を砕くために我は来た！
Come, Wang Qi!
I have come here to crush you!
Pang Nuan, too!
龐煖も！
あっ… 王騎将軍も出た！
General Wang Qi is going now, too!
（趙兵たち）龐煖さま！
Lord Pang Nuan!
（王騎軍兵たち）王騎将軍！
General Wang Qi!
ウリャーッ！
（龐煖）元の体に戻るのに３年
It took three years before my body returned to normal
山中で修練を６年積んだ
and then I underwent six years of training in the mountains.
そして 李牧(りぼく)という男が現れた
Then a man named Li Mu appeared.
話に乗ったのは―
The reason I went along with it was because of my extreme self-confidence
この男など足元にも及ばぬ極みに
達した自負があったからだ
that this man does not even come close to me.
Confidence in an extreme level of military might that almost no human can reach.
およそ人の到達できぬ武の極みに
だが なぜ…
Yet, why...
Why is repelling this man's blade so impossible...?
（龐煖）この男の刃(やいば)は
はじき返すことがかなわぬほどに…
こうも重い？
And why is mine so heavy?!
この男のどこに こんな力が…
Where did this man get such power?!
腑(ふ)に落ちないようですね 龐煖
It seems you do not understand, Pang Nuan.
武将とは やっかいなものですよ
Being a military commander is a dangerous thing.
13のころより
数えきれぬほどの戦場を駆け回り
Since age 13, I ran through a countless number of battlefields.
数万の友を失い
数十万の敵を葬ってきました
I lost some tens of thousands of comrades in arms and interred some hundreds of thousands of enemies.
命の火と共に消えた彼らの思いが
Their thoughts and feelings disappeared with their flames of life,
but they all still dwell heavily on these shoulders.
全て
この双肩に重く宿っているのですよ
もちろん摎の思いもです！
And of course, so do the feelings of Liao!
山でひとり籠もっているあなたには
理解できないことでしょうね
Someone like you who secluded themselves in the mountains cannot understand that, yes?
The feelings of the dead are on his shoulders?
（尾平(びへい)）
死んだヤツらの思いが双肩に…
（信）そのとおりだ
だから 俺らは強くなるし―
That's right. That's why we get stronger
そこを通ってきた将軍ってのは
強(つえ)えんだ！
and why the generals, that have gone through that so much, are so strong.
（龐煖）語るに足らぬ
Worthless banter.
いつの時代も
お前たちは思い違いをしている
No matter the era, you all are under the same misapprehension.
死者の思いを継ぐなど
残された者の勝手な夢想
Succeeding the feelings of the dead is nothing but a selfish delusion of those that survive.
人は死ねば土くれと化す
When people die, they turn to lumps of earth.
敗者は地に落ち 勝者は天に近づく
The losers fall to earth and the victors get closer to heaven.
That is all that exists!
あることわりは それだけだ！
Pang Nuan...
（王騎）龐煖
やはり あなたとは
最後まで相いれないようですね
It seems that to the very end, we will not see eye to eye.
当然だ！
Of course!
王騎が愛した女 摎
The woman Wang Qi loved, Liao.
それを殺した龐煖
And the man that killed him, Pang Nuan.
そこまでの因縁があったからこそ
趙軍は龐煖を総大将に据えた…
Because such a connection existed, the Zhao Army placed Pang Nuan as their Supreme Commander
in order to lure Wang Qi onto the battlefield...
王騎を戦場に引きずり出すために…
大王？
（政）いや まさか…
My king?
No... It can't be...
この５日間に及ぶ戦い
This battle that's spanned for five days...
全ては王騎将軍の命がねらい…
All of it was to take General Wang Qi's life?
Defeating the Great General in order to reach victory is a basic truth of war.
（昌文君）勝利のために
大将を討つは そもそも戦の道理
（政）いや そうではない
No, that's not what I mean.
この戦
もっと異様な形をしているのだ
This war takes on a stranger form.
勝利のために
王騎を討とうというのではない
They are not trying to kill Wang Qi in order to obtain victory.
そもそも王騎の首こそが ねらい
Their primary goal is Wang Qi's head.
そのための戦いなのだ
（昌文君）まさか…
That is why they are fighting.
Could that be...?
It sounds far-fetched at first,
（政）にわかには信じられぬ
だが ここまでの策を巡らせたのが
李牧という男なら…
but seeing as the one who established the plan so far has been that man, Li Mu...
（側近Ａ）突破されました！
They broke through!
The third formation has collapsed!
（副官）第３陣 崩壊です！
（側近Ｃ）何なのだ？ あの男は
What is that man?!
H-How can this be...?
（趙荘(ちょうそう)）な… なんということだ…
これほどのバケモノだったとは…
He was this much of a monster?
（趙兵たち）ウワーッ！
（趙荘）
王騎め あえて隠しておったな！
That Wang Qi was hiding this?!
I am faster and my strength is higher as well.
（龐煖）
我のほうが速く 力も我のほうが上
In terms of technique, it's incomparable.
技においては比べるまでもない
（斬る音）
（渕）ああ 王騎将軍！
General Wang Qi!
Yet why can I not cut him down?!
なのに なぜ斬り伏せられぬ？
敗れた理由は―
If you want to know why you lost,
あの世で摎に教えてもらいなさい！
have Liao tell you in the next world!
いけー！
Go!
（信）ど… どうしたんだ 王騎将軍
なんで？
Wh-What happened, General Wang Qi?
Why?!
待て
さっきから何だ？ この地鳴りは
Wait.
I've felt it for a while, what is this rumbling in the ground?
（政）王騎よ
Wang Qi... Just what level of trap are you now entwined in?
今 お前は どれほどのワナに
からめ捕られているのか
But... Don't die, Wang Qi!
だが 死ぬな 王騎よ！
早かったですね 随分
You're early... Very much so...
信 王騎の運命(さだめ)を変えてくれ！
Xin. Change Wang Qi's fate!
赤き　血潮
akaki chishio
Crimson blood flowing...
この鼓動は　野望なのか
kono kodou wa yabou na no ka
Is this racing pulse ambition?
幼き日　誓った
osanaki hi chigatta
Even now, I do not waver
夢は今も　揺るがない
yume wa ima mo yuru ga nai
from that dream I dedicated myself to in my youth.
命が燃える
inochi ga moeru
My life burns bright.
Ｎｅｖｅｒ　Ｅｎｄｉｎｇ　Ｓｏｕｌ　情熱よ
Never Ending Soul jounetsu yo
Never Ending Soul of passion,
導け　天地を拓け
michibike tenchi wo hirake
guide me and open the path to heaven.
Ｎｅｖｅｒ　Ｅｎｄｉｎｇ　Ｗｏｒｌｄ　打ち立てよう
Never Ending World uchitateyou
Let's create a Never Ending World!
永遠の絆が誇り
eien no kizuna ga hokori
Boasting an eternal bond,
おまえと夢見た世界を　この手に　掴もう
omae to yumemita sekai wo kono te ni tsukamou
you and I will grasp the world we dreamed of.
～♪
Preview
For the first time in quite a while
（王騎）
久しぶりに血が沸き立ちます！
my blood is seething!
With no means of escape,
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）活路なし！
天下を震わせた怪鳥が地に落ちる！
the mystery bird that made the heaven's temple
I am at the
Verge of Death
falls to earth!
End
I am at the
Verge of Death
次回 “我 死線にあり”
Next time,